{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcG9ydHMgaXMgbm90IHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIHRyaWF0aGxvbj8=","correct_answer":"SG9yc2UtUmlkaW5n","incorrect_answers":["Q3ljbGluZw==","U3dpbW1pbmc=","UnVubmluZw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgcmVsZWFzZWQ\/","correct_answer":"MjAwNw==","incorrect_answers":["MjAwOQ==","MjAwNQ==","MjAxMA=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzICBwYXJlbnRzPw==","correct_answer":"VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh","incorrect_answers":["Sm9leSAmIEphY2tpZQ==","SmFzb24gJiBTYXJhaA==","VG9kZCAmIE1pcmE="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb21tb24gc3VybmFtZSBXYWxlcz8=","correct_answer":"Sm9uZXM=","incorrect_answers":["V2lsbGlhbXM=","RGF2aWVz","RXZhbnM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggQ2FuYWRpYW4gcmVnZ2FlIG11c2ljaWFuIGhhZCBhIDE5OTMgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcgJ0luZm9ybWVyJz8=","correct_answer":"U25vdw==","incorrect_answers":["UmFpbg==","SGFpbA==","U2xlZXQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHN0YXJyZWQgaW4gdGhlIGZpbG0gMTk3MyBtb3ZpZSAiRW50ZXIgVGhlIERyYWdvbiI\/","correct_answer":"QnJ1Y2UgTGVl","incorrect_answers":["SmFja2llIENoYW4=","SmV0IExp","IFl1bi1GYXQgQ2hvdw=="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggR2VybWFuIGZpZWxkIG1hcnNoYWwgd2FzIGtub3duIGFzIHRoZSBgRGVzZXJ0IEZveGA\/","correct_answer":"RXJ3aW4gUm9tbWVs","incorrect_answers":["RXJuc3QgQnVzY2g=","V29sZnJhbSBGcmVpaGVyciB2b24gUmljaHRob2Zlbg==","V2lsaGVsbSBMaXN0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2F0Y2hwaHJhc2UgdXNlZCBieSBSaWNrIFNhbmNoZXogaW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5Ij8=","correct_answer":"U2xhbSBkdW5rLCBub3RoaW5nIGJ1dCBuZXQh","incorrect_answers":["SGl0IHRoZSBzYWNrLCBKYWNrIQ==","Umlra2ktVGlra2ktVGF2aSwgYmlhdGNoIQ==","V3ViYmEtbHViYmEtZHViLWR1YiE="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"QXJlYSA1MSBpcyBsb2NhdGVkIGluIHdoaWNoIFVTIHN0YXRlPw==","correct_answer":"TmV2YWRh","incorrect_answers":["QXJpem9uYQ==","TmV3IE1leGljbw==","VXRhaA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYmVzdCBzZWxsaW5nIGFsYnVtIG9mIGFsbCB0aW1lPw==","correct_answer":"VGhyaWxsZXI=","incorrect_answers":["QmFjayBpbiBCbGFjaw==","QWJiZXkgUm9hZA==","VGhlIERhcmsgU2lkZSBvZiB0aGUgTW9vbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hlcmUgZG9lcyB0aGUgTWFjIHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIG5hbWUgRmxlZXR3b29kIE1hYyBjb21lIGZyb20\/","correct_answer":"Sm9obiBNY1ZpZQ==","incorrect_answers":["Q2hyaXN0aW5lIE1jVmll","TWFjIE1jQW5hbGx5","RGF2aWQgVGVubmFudA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBzdGFyIG9mIHRoZSBBTUMgc2VyaWVzIEJyZWFraW5nIEJhZD8=","correct_answer":"V2FsdGVyIFdoaXRl","incorrect_answers":["U2F1bCBHb29kbWFu","SmVzc2UgUGlua21hbg==","U2t5bGVyIFdoaXRl"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gS2luZ2RvbSBIZWFydHMsIGhvdyBtYW55IG1lbWJlcnMgZG9lcyBPcmdhbml6YXRpb24gWElJSSBoYXZlIGluIHRvdGFsPw==","correct_answer":"MTQ=","incorrect_answers":["MTA=","MTM=","MTI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggbWVtYmVyIG9mIHRoZSBGb28gRmlnaHRlcnMgd2FzIHByZXZpb3VzbHkgdGhlIGRydW1tZXIgZm9yIE5pcnZhbmE\/","correct_answer":"RGF2ZSBHcm9obA==","incorrect_answers":["VGF5bG9yIEhhd2tpbnM=","TmF0ZSBNZW5kZWw=","Q2hyaXMgU2hpZmxldHQ="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIHNlcmllcyBvZiB0aGUgSW50ZWwgSEQgZ3JhcGhpY3MgZ2VuZXJhdGlvbiBzdWNjZWVkaW5nIHRoYXQgb2YgdGhlIDUwMDAgYW5kIDYwMDAgc2VyaWVzIChCcm9hZHdlbGwpIGlzIGNhbGxlZDo=","correct_answer":"SEQgR3JhcGhpY3MgNTAw","incorrect_answers":["SEQgR3JhcGhpY3MgNzAwIA==","SEQgR3JhcGhpY3MgNjAw","SEQgR3JhcGhpY3MgNzAwMA=="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgb25seSBzdGF0ZSBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcyB0aGF0IGRvZXMgbm90IGhhdmUgYSBmbGFnIGluIGEgc2hhcGUgd2l0aCA0IGVkZ2VzPw==","correct_answer":"T2hpbw==","incorrect_answers":["RmxvcmlkYQ==","SWRhaG8=","TmV3IE1leGljbw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQm9qYWNrIEhvcnNlbWFuIGNoYXJhY3RlcnMgaXMgYSBodW1hbj8=","correct_answer":"VG9kZCBDaGF2ZXo=","incorrect_answers":["TGVubmllIFR1cnRsZXRhdWI=","UHJpbmNlc3MgQ2Fyb2x5bg==","VG9tIEp1bWJvLUdydW1ibw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gIkludXlhc2hhIiwgd2hhdCBhcmUgdGhlIGhlcm9zIGFyZSBsb29raW5nIHRvIGNvbGxlY3Q\/","correct_answer":"SmV3ZWwgU2hhcmRz","incorrect_answers":["RHJhZ29uIEJhbGxz","UmF2ZSBTdG9uZXM=","U2FjcmVkIFN0b25lcw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBkb2VzIElXSEJZRCBzdGFuZCBmb3Igb24gdGhlIHNrdWxsIGluIHRoZSBIYWxvIHNlcmllcz8=","correct_answer":"SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJlZW4gWW91ciBEYWRkeQ==","incorrect_answers":["SSBXYW5uYSBIYXZlIEJhYmllcyBZb3UgRG93bg==","SSBXb3VsZCBIYXRlIEJlaW5nIFlvdXIgRHJpdmVy","SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJvdWdodCBZb3VyIERvZw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDl0aCBQb2tlbW9uIG1vdmllLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIFByaW5jZSBvZiB0aGUgU2VhPw==","correct_answer":"TWFuYXBoeQ==","incorrect_answers":["QXNo","TWF5","UGhhbnRvbQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgU3RhcmJvdW5kIHJhY2VzIGhhcyBhIFdpbGQgV2VzdCBjdWx0dXJlPw==","correct_answer":"Tm92YWtpZA==","incorrect_answers":["QXZpYW4=","SHVtYW4=","SHlsb3Rs"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0IGdhbWUgb2YgdGhlIFNseSBDb29wZXIgZnJhbmNoaXNlLCB3aGF0IGZhbWlseSBoZWlybG9vbSBkaWQgU2x5IENvb3BlciB3YW50IHRvIHN0ZWFsIGJhY2s\/","correct_answer":"VGhpZXZpdXMgUmFjY29vbnVz","incorrect_answers":["UmFjY29vbiBUcmFpbmluZyAxMDE=","VGhlIEFydCBvZiBTbmVhaw==","UmFjY29vbnVzIFRlYWNodXM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gUG9ydGFsIDIsIGhvdyBkaWQgQ0VPIG9mIEFwZXJ0dXJlIFNjaWVuY2UsIENhdmUgSm9obnNvbiwgcHJlc3VtYWJseSBkaWU\/","correct_answer":"TW9vbiBSb2NrIFBvaXNvbmluZw==","incorrect_answers":["QWNjaWRlbnRhbGx5IHNlbmRpbmcgYSBwb3J0YWwgdG8gdGhlIE1vb24=","U2xpcHBlZCBpbiB0aGUgc2hvd2Vy","QXNiZXN0b3MgUG9pc29uaW5n"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBUZWFtIEZvcnRyZXNzIDIgU2NvdXQncyBjaXR5IG9mIG9yaWdpbj8=","correct_answer":"Qm9zdG9u","incorrect_answers":["U3lkbmV5","RGV0cm9pdA==","TmV3IFlvcms="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCwiIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgdHdvIEF1c3RyYWxpYW4gY3JpbWluYWxzIGZyb20gdGhlIEp1bmtlcnMgZmFjdGlvbj8=","correct_answer":"SnVua3JhdCBhbmQgUm9hZGhvZw==","incorrect_answers":["Um9hZHJhdCBhbmQgSnVua2hvZw==","QW5hIGFuZCBQaGFyYWg=","TWNDcmVlIGFuZCBEZWFkZXll"]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiB0aGUgU29tbWUgYmVnaW4\/","correct_answer":"SnVseSAxc3QsIDE5MTY=","incorrect_answers":["QXVndXN0IDFzdCwgMTkxNg==","SnVseSAybmQsIDE5MTY=","SnVuZSAzMHRoLCAxOTE2"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIDIwMTEgVmlkZW8gR2FtZSAiTWluZWNyYWZ0Ij8=","correct_answer":"TWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24=","incorrect_answers":["SmVucyBCZXJnZW5zdGVu","RGFuaWVsIFJvc2VuZmVsZA==","Q2FybCBNYW5uZWg="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gVW5kZXJ0YWxlLCB3aGF0J3MgdGhlIHByaXplIGZvciBhbnN3ZXJpbmcgY29ycmVjdGx5Pw==","correct_answer":"TW9yZSBxdWVzdGlvbnM=","incorrect_answers":["TmV3IGNhcg==","TWVyY3k=","TW9uZXk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"R3V5J3MgR3JvY2VyeSBHYW1lcyBpcyBob3N0ZWQgYnkgd2hpY2ggcHJlc2VudGVyPw==","correct_answer":"R3V5IEZpZXJp","incorrect_answers":["R3V5IE1hcnRpbg==","R3V5IFJpdGNoaWU=","QWluc2xleSBIYXJyaW90dA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgYSBzb25nIGJ5IFRlYXJzIGZvciBGZWFycz8=","correct_answer":"U2hvdXQ=","incorrect_answers":["U2NyZWFt","WWVsbA==","U2hyaWVr"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgTnVjbGVhciBUaHJvbmUsIHdoYXQgY2hhcmFjdGVyIGlzIG9ubHkgdXNhYmxlIGluIGEgcGxheSB0aHJvdWdoIHdpdGggTWVsdGluZz8=","correct_answer":"U2tlbGV0b24=","incorrect_answers":["RnJvZw==","SG9ycm9y","UGxhbnQ="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIGJpZ2dlc3QgZGlzdGluY3Rpb24gYmV0d2VlbiBhIGV1a2FyeW90aWMgY2VsbCBhbmQgYSBwcm9rYXJ5b3RpYyBjZWxsIGlzOg==","correct_answer":"VGhlIHByZXNlbmNlIG9yIGFic2VuY2Ugb2YgYSBudWNsZXVz","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIG92ZXJhbGwgc2l6ZQ==","VGhlIHByZXNlbmNlIG9yIGFic2VuY2Ugb2YgY2VydGFpbiBvcmdhbmVsbGVz","VGhlIG1vZGUgb2YgcmVwcm9kdWN0aW9u"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGluIFB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiBzYXlzICJObywgdGhleSBnb3QgdGhlIG1ldHJpYyBzeXN0ZW0gdGhlcmUsIHRoZXkgd291bGRuJ3Qga25vdyB3aGF0IHRoZSBmdWNrIGEgUXVhcnRlciBQb3VuZGVyIGlzLiI=","correct_answer":"VmluY2VudCBWZWdh","incorrect_answers":["SnVsZXMgV2lubmZpZWxk","SmltbWllIERpbW1pY2s=","QnV0Y2ggQ29vbGlkZ2U="]},{"category":"QW5pbWFscw==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyBHcnVtcHkgQ2F0J3MgcmVhbCBuYW1lPw==","correct_answer":"VGFyZGFyIFNhdWNl","incorrect_answers":["U2F1Y2U=","TWlubmll","QnJvY2NvbGk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcHJvdGFnb25pc3Qgb2YgSi5ELiBTYWxpbmdlcidzIG5vdmVsIENhdGNoZXIgaW4gdGhlIFJ5ZT8=","correct_answer":"SG9sZGVuIENhdWxmaWVsZA==","incorrect_answers":["RmxldGNoZXIgQ2hyaXN0aWFu","SmF5IEdhdHNieQ==","UmFuZGFsbCBGbGFnZw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggODBzIGJhbmQgaXMgZnJvbnRlZCBieSBzaW5nZXIvZ3VpdGFyaXN0IFJvYmVydCBTbWl0aD8=","correct_answer":"VGhlIEN1cmU=","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIFNtaXRocw==","RWNobyAmIHRoZSBCdW5ueW1lbg==","TmV3IE9yZGVy"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGFyZSB0aGUgb3JpZ2luYWwgY3JlYXRvcnMgb2YgUmFjaGV0ICYgQ2xhbms\/","correct_answer":"SW5zb21uaWFjIEdhbWVz","incorrect_answers":["UGl4ZWxUYWlsIEdhbWVz","UmFyZQ==","QmV0aGVzZGE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gUG9rZW1vbiBSZWQgJiBCbHVlLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEhNMDU\/","correct_answer":"Rmxhc2g=","incorrect_answers":["U3RyZW5ndGg=","Q3V0","Rmx5"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWF4aW11bSBIUCBpbiBUZXJyYXJpYT8=","correct_answer":"NTAw","incorrect_answers":["NDAw","MTAwMA==","MTAw"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBjb2xsYWJvcmF0aXZlIGFsYnVtIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBieSBLYW55ZSBXZXN0IGFuZCBKYXktWiBpbiAyMDExPw==","correct_answer":"V2F0Y2ggdGhlIFRocm9uZQ==","incorrect_answers":["RGlzdGFudCBSZWxhdGl2ZXM=","V2hhdCBhIFRpbWUgdG8gYmUgQWxpdmU=","VW5maW5pc2hlZCBCdXNpbmVzcw=="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiB0aGUgVVMgU3RhdGUgb2YgTmV3IFlvcms\/","correct_answer":"QWxiYW55","incorrect_answers":["QnVmZmFsbw==","TmV3IFlvcms=","Um9jaGVzdGVy"]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IHdhcyBTb2NyYXRlcyBleGVjdXRlZD8=","correct_answer":"UG9pc29u","incorrect_answers":["RGVjYXBpdGF0aW9u","RmlyaW5nIHNxdWFk","Q3J1Y2lmaXhpb24g"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gIkJyZWFraW5nIEJhZCIsIFdhbHRlciBXaGl0ZSBpcyBhIGhpZ2ggc2Nob29sIHRlYWNoZXIgZGlhZ25vc2VkIHdpdGggd2hpY2ggZm9ybSBvZiBjYW5jZXI\/","correct_answer":"THVuZyBDYW5jZXI=","incorrect_answers":["UHJvc3RhdGUgQ2FuY2Vy","QnJhaW4gQ2FuY2Vy","VGVzdGljdWxhciBDYW5jZXI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyBFdmVyZXN0J3MgZmF2b3JpdGUgZm9vZCBpbiB0aGUgTmlja2Vsb2Rlb24vTmljayBKci4gc2VyaWVzICJQQVcgUGF0cm9sIj8=","correct_answer":"TGl2ZXI=","incorrect_answers":["Q2hpY2tlbg==","U3RlYWs=","Q2FyaWJvdQ=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjYXJkIGdhbWVzIHJldm9sdmVzIGFyb3VuZCBudW1iZXJzIGFuZCBiYXNpYyBtYXRoPw==","correct_answer":"VW5v","incorrect_answers":["R28gRmlzaA==","VHdpc3Rlcg==","TXVuY2hraW4="]},{"category":"TXl0aG9sb2d5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXl0aG9sb2dpY2FsIGNyZWF0dXJlcyBpcyBzYWlkIHRvIGJlIGhhbGYtbWFuIGFuZCBoYWxmLWhvcnNlPw==","correct_answer":"Q2VudGF1cg==","incorrect_answers":["TWlub3RhdXI=","UGVnYXN1cw==","R29yZ29u"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcGxhbmV0IHRoYXQgdGhlIERvY3RvciBmcm9tIHRlbGV2aXNpb24gc2VyaWVzICJEb2N0b3IgV2hvIiBjb21lcyBmcm9tPw==","correct_answer":"R2FsbGlmcmV5","incorrect_answers":["U29udGFy","U2thcm8=","TW9uZGFz"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZ2FtZSBkZXZlbG9wZXIgd2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyI\/","correct_answer":"VHJleWFyY2g=","incorrect_answers":["U2xlZGdlaGFtbWVyIEdhbWVz","SW5maW5pdHkgV2FyZA==","TmF1Z2h0eSBEb2c="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYm9zcyByb3VuZCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIgbWFwICJGaXZlIj8=","correct_answer":"VGhlIFBlbnRhZ29uIFRoaWVm","incorrect_answers":["SGVsbGhvdW5kcw==","SnVtcGluZyBKYWNrcw==","TmFwYWxtIFpvbWJpZQ=="]},{"category":"TXl0aG9sb2d5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBteXRob2xvZ3kgZGlkIHRoZSBnb2QgIkFwb2xsbyIgY29tZSBmcm9tPw==","correct_answer":"R3JlZWsgYW5kIFJvbWFu","incorrect_answers":["Um9tYW4gYW5kIFNwYW5pc2g=","R3JlZWsgYW5kIENoaW5lc2U=","R3JlZWssIFJvbWFuIGFuZCBOb3JzZQ=="]},
{"category":"QXJ0","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHBhaW50ZWQgdGhlIE1vbmEgTGlzYT8=","correct_answer":"TGVvbmFyZG8gZGEgVmluY2k=","incorrect_answers":["UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw==","Q2xhdWRlIE1vbmV0","VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBib25lcyBpcyBub3QgaW4gdGhlIGxlZz8=","correct_answer":"UmFkaXVz","incorrect_answers":["UGF0ZWxsYQ==","VGliaWE=","RmlidWxhIA=="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBzcG9ydHMgaXMgbm90IHBhcnQgb2YgdGhlIHRyaWF0aGxvbj8=","correct_answer":"SG9yc2UtUmlkaW5n","incorrect_answers":["Q3ljbGluZw==","U3dpbW1pbmc=","UnVubmluZw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvJ3MgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBUaHJhbGwgaW4gdGhlIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzPw==","correct_answer":"Q2hyaXMgTWV0emVu","incorrect_answers":["QmVuIEFmZmxlY2s=","SmFzb24gRGVydWxv","SmltIENhcnJleQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdyb3RlIGFuZCBkaXJlY3RlZCB0aGUgMTk4NiBmaWxtICdQbGF0b29uJz8=","correct_answer":"T2xpdmVyIFN0b25l","incorrect_answers":["RnJhbmNpcyBGb3JkIENvcHBvbGE=","U3RhbmxleSBLdWJyaWNr","TWljaGFlbCBDaW1pbm8="]},{"category":"Q2VsZWJyaXRpZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"TmFtZWQgYWZ0ZXIgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXIgaGUgcGxheWVkIGluIGEgMTk2OSBmaWxtLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBza2kgcmVzb3J0IGluIFV0YWggdGhhdCBSb2JlcnQgUmVkZm9yZCBib3VnaHQgaW4gMTk2OD8=","correct_answer":"U3VuZGFuY2U=","incorrect_answers":["V29vZHdhcmQ=","VHVybmVy","Qm9va2Vy"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBkYW5jZWQgdGhlIHR3aXN0IHdpdGggSm9obiBUcmF2b2x0YSBpbiAnUHVscCBGaWN0aW9uJz8=","correct_answer":"VW1hIFRodXJtYW4=","incorrect_answers":["S2F0aHkgR3JpZmZpbg==","UGFtIEdyaWVy","QnJpZGdldCBGb25kYQ=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggYmVzdCBzZWxsaW5nIHRveSBvZiAxOTgzIGNhdXNlZCBoeXN0ZXJpYSwgcmVzdWx0aW5nIGluIHJpb3RzIGJyZWFraW5nIG91dCBpbiBzdG9yZXM\/","correct_answer":"Q2FiYmFnZSBQYXRjaCBLaWRz","incorrect_answers":["VHJhbnNmb3JtZXJz","Q2FyZSBCZWFycw==","UnViaWvigJlzIEN1YmU="]},{"category":"VmVoaWNsZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIEl0YWxpYW4gYXV0b21ha2VyIExhbWJvcmdoaW5pIHVzZXMgd2hhdCBhbmltYWwgYXMgaXRzIGxvZ28\/","correct_answer":"QnVsbA==","incorrect_answers":["QmF0","SG9yc2U=","U25ha2U="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgY2F0Y2hwaHJhc2UgdXNlZCBieSBSaWNrIFNhbmNoZXogaW4gdGhlIFRWIHNob3cgIlJpY2sgYW5kIE1vcnR5Ij8=","correct_answer":"U2xhbSBkdW5rLCBub3RoaW5nIGJ1dCBuZXQh","incorrect_answers":["SGl0IHRoZSBzYWNrLCBKYWNrIQ==","Umlra2ktVGlra2ktVGF2aSwgYmlhdGNoIQ==","V3ViYmEtbHViYmEtZHViLWR1YiE="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gcGFzdCB0aW1lcywgd2hhdCB3b3VsZCBhIGdlbnRsZW1hbiBrZWVwIGluIGhpcyBmb2IgcG9ja2V0Pw==","correct_answer":"V2F0Y2g=","incorrect_answers":["TW9uZXk=","S2V5cw==","Tm90ZWJvb2s="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgInBvd2VyaG91c2UiIG9mIHRoZSBFdWthcnlvdGljIGFuaW1hbCBjZWxsPw==","correct_answer":"TWl0b2Nob25kcmlh","incorrect_answers":["TnVjbGV1cw==","Q2hsb3JvcGxhc3Q=","RW5kb3BsYXNtaWMgUmV0aWN1bHVt"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB3cml0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSI\/","correct_answer":"TWFyYyBMYWlkbGF3","incorrect_answers":["R2FiZSBOZXdlbGw=","Um9iaW4gV2Fsa2Vy","Q2hldCBGYWxpc3plaw=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcG93ZXJob3VzZSBvZiB0aGUgY2VsbD8=","correct_answer":"TWl0b2Nob25kcmlh","incorrect_answers":["Umlib3NvbWU=","UmVkYnVsbA==","TnVjbGV1cw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgRGlzbmV5IGNhcnRvb24gY2hhcmFjdGVyPw==","correct_answer":"RGFmZnkgRHVjaw==","incorrect_answers":["RG9uYWxkIER1Y2s=","RGFpc3kgRHVjaw==","U2Nyb29nZSBNY0R1Y2s="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2hhcGUgb2YgdGhlIHRveSBpbnZlbnRlZCBieSBIdW5nYXJpYW4gcHJvZmVzc29yIEVybsWRIFJ1YmlrPw==","correct_answer":"Q3ViZQ==","incorrect_answers":["U3BoZXJl","Q3lsaW5kZXI=","UHlyYW1pZA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiAiQXJraGFtIiBzZXJpZXM\/","correct_answer":"QXJraGFtIEFzeWx1bQ==","incorrect_answers":["QXJraGFtIEtuaWdodA==","QXJraGFtIENpdHk=","QXJraGFtIE9yaWdpbnM="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIG9yaWdpbmFsIFJvbWFuIGFscGhhYmV0IGxhY2tlZCB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIGxldHRlcnMgRVhDRVBUOg==","correct_answer":"WA==","incorrect_answers":["Vw==","VQ==","Sg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiBGaW5uaXNoIERKIERhcnVkZSdzIGhpdCBzaW5nbGUgcmVsZWFzZWQgaW4gT2N0b2JlciAxOTk5Pw==","correct_answer":"U2FuZHN0b3Jt","incorrect_answers":["RHVzdCBEZXZpbA==","U2lyb2Njbw==","S2hhbXNpbg=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIGFuaW1hbCB3YXMgSGFyYW1iZSwgd2hvIHdhcyBzaG90IGFmdGVyIGEgY2hpbGQgZmVsbCBpbnRvIGl0J3MgZW5jbG9zdXJlIGF0IHRoZSBDaW5jaW5uYXRpIFpvbz8=","correct_answer":"R29yaWxsYQ==","incorrect_answers":["VGlnZXI=","UGFuZGE=","Q3JvY29kaWxl"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEphbWVzIEJvbmQgZmlsbT8=","correct_answer":"RHIuIE5v","incorrect_answers":["R29sZGZpbmdlcg==","RnJvbSBSdXNzaWEgV2l0aCBMb3Zl","VGh1bmRlcmJhbGw="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGFydGlmaWNpYWwgRWFydGggc2F0ZWxsaXRlLCBsYXVuY2hlZCBieSB0aGUgU292aWV0IFVuaW9uIGluIDE5NTc\/","correct_answer":"U3B1dG5payAx","incorrect_answers":["U295dXogN0stT0s=","WmVuaXQtMg==","Vm9za2hvZCAzS1Y="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBkb2VzIElXSEJZRCBzdGFuZCBmb3Igb24gdGhlIHNrdWxsIGluIHRoZSBIYWxvIHNlcmllcz8=","correct_answer":"SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJlZW4gWW91ciBEYWRkeQ==","incorrect_answers":["SSBXYW5uYSBIYXZlIEJhYmllcyBZb3UgRG93bg==","SSBXb3VsZCBIYXRlIEJlaW5nIFlvdXIgRHJpdmVy","SSBXb3VsZCBIYXZlIEJvdWdodCBZb3VyIERvZw=="]},{"category":"VmVoaWNsZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBjb2xsaXNpb24gYXZvaWRhbmNlIHN5c3RlbXMgaGVscHMgYWlycGxhbmVzIGF2b2lkIGNvbGxpZGluZyB3aXRoIGVhY2ggb3RoZXI\/","correct_answer":"VENBUw==","incorrect_answers":["R1BXUw==","T0NBUw==","VEFXUw=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBjaGVtaWNhbCBlbGVtZW50IEN1cml1bSBuYW1lZCBhZnRlcj8=","correct_answer":"TWFyaWUgJiBQaWVycmUgQ3VyaWU=","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIEN1cmlvc2l0eSBSb3Zlcg==","Q3VyaW91cyBHZW9yZ2U=","U3RlcGhlbiBDdXJyeQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHN1YmplY3Qgb2YgdGhlIDIwMTQgc29uZyAiQ29DbyIgYnkgQW1lcmljYW4gcmFwcGVyIE8uIFQuIEdlbmFzaXM\/","correct_answer":"Q29jYWluZQ==","incorrect_answers":["Q29uYW4gTydCcmllbg==","Q29iYWx0KElJKSBjYXJib25hdGU=","Q29jb251dCBjcmVhbSBwaWU="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggVUsgY291bnRyeSBmZWF0dXJlcyBhIGRyYWdvbiBvbiB0aGVpciBmbGFnPw==","correct_answer":"V2FsZXM=","incorrect_answers":["RW5nbGFuZA==","Tm9ydGggSXJlbGFuZA==","U2NvdGxhbmQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlICJLIiBpbiAiSy1Qb3AiIHN0YW5kcyBmb3Igd2hpY2ggd29yZD8=","correct_answer":"S29yZWFu","incorrect_answers":["S2VueWFu","S2F6YWtoc3Rhbg==","S3V3YWl0aQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggTWFyaW8gc3Bpbi1vZmYgZ2FtZSBkaWQgV2FsdWlnaSBtYWtlIGhpcyBkZWJ1dD8=","correct_answer":"TWFyaW8gVGVubmlz","incorrect_answers":["TWFyaW8gUGFydHkgMw==","TWFyaW8gS2FydDogRG91YmxlIERhc2ghIQ==","TWFyaW8gR29sZjogVG9hZHN0b29sIFRvdXI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIiBlbnRlciBjbG9zZWQgYmV0YT8=","correct_answer":"MjAxNQ==","incorrect_answers":["MjAxMw==","MjAxMQ==","MjAxNg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hlbiB3YXMgTWluZWNyYWZ0IGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIHRvIHRoZSBwdWJsaWM\/","correct_answer":"TWF5IDE3dGgsIDIwMDk=","incorrect_answers":["U2VwdGVtYmVyIDE3dGgsIDIwMDk=","Tm92ZW1iZXIgMTh0aCwgMjAxMQ==","T2N0b2JlciA3dGgsIDIwMTE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIDIwMTEgVmlkZW8gR2FtZSAiTWluZWNyYWZ0Ij8=","correct_answer":"TWFya3VzIFBlcnNzb24=","incorrect_answers":["SmVucyBCZXJnZW5zdGVu","RGFuaWVsIFJvc2VuZmVsZA==","Q2FybCBNYW5uZWg="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gMTcyMCwgRW5nbGFuZCB3YXMgaW4gbWFzc2l2ZSBkZWJ0LCBhbmQgYmVjYW1lIGluIGludm9sdmVkIGluIHRoZSBTb3V0aCBTZWEgQnViYmxlLiBXaG8gd2FzIHRoZSBtYWluIG1hc3Rlcm1pbmQgYmVoaW5kIGl0Pw==","correct_answer":"Sm9obiBCbHVudA==","incorrect_answers":["RGFuaWVsIERlZm9l","Um9iZXJ0IEhhcmxleQ==","Sm9obiBDaHVyY2hpbGw="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBpcyBOT1QgYSBzdW1tb24gaW4gdGhlIGdhbWUgIlNvdXRoIFBhcms6IFRoZSBTdGljayBvZiBUcnV0aCI\/","correct_answer":"VG93ZWxpZQ==","incorrect_answers":["SmVzdXM=","TXIuIEhhbmtleQ==","TXIuIFNsYXZl"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdhcyB0aGUgYXV0aG9yIG9mIHRoZSAxOTU0IG5vdmVsLCAiTG9yZCBvZiB0aGUgRmxpZXMiPw==","correct_answer":"V2lsbGlhbSBHb2xkaW5n","incorrect_answers":["U3RlcGhlbiBLaW5n","Ri4gU2NvdHQgRml0emdlcmFsZA==","SHVudGVyIEZveA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIHNwYXJrZWQgY29udHJvdmVyc3kgYmVjYXVzZSBvZiBpdHMgaGlkZGVuICJIb3QgQ29mZmVlIiBtaW5pZ2FtZT8=","correct_answer":"R3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogU2FuIEFuZHJlYXM=","incorrect_answers":["R3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0bzogVmljZSBDaXR5","SGl0bWFuOiBCbG9vZCBNb25leQ==","Q29va2luZyBNYW1h"]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggdGVhbSB3b24gMjAxNCBGSUZBIFdvcmxkIEN1cCBpbiBCcmF6aWw\/","correct_answer":"R2VybWFueQ==","incorrect_answers":["QXJnZW50aW5h","QnJhemls","TmV0aGVybGFuZHM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBjb2xsYWJvcmF0aXZlIGFsYnVtIHdhcyByZWxlYXNlZCBieSBLYW55ZSBXZXN0IGFuZCBKYXktWiBpbiAyMDExPw==","correct_answer":"V2F0Y2ggdGhlIFRocm9uZQ==","incorrect_answers":["RGlzdGFudCBSZWxhdGl2ZXM=","V2hhdCBhIFRpbWUgdG8gYmUgQWxpdmU=","VW5maW5pc2hlZCBCdXNpbmVzcw=="]},{"category":"TXl0aG9sb2d5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gbW9zdCB0cmFkaXRpb25zLCB3aG8gd2FzIHRoZSB3aWZlIG9mIFpldXM\/","correct_answer":"SGVyYQ==","incorrect_answers":["QXBocm9kaXRl","QXRoZW5h","SGVzdGlh"]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhcnMgYXJlIGZlYXR1cmVkIG9uIE5ldyBaZWFsYW5kJ3MgZmxhZz8=","correct_answer":"NA==","incorrect_answers":["NQ==","Mg==","MA=="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IG1hbnkgY291bnRyaWVzIGRvZXMgTWV4aWNvIGJvcmRlcj8=","correct_answer":"Mw==","incorrect_answers":["Mg==","NA==","MQ=="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBKYXBhbmVzZSBpc2xhbmRzIGlzIHRoZSBiaWdnZXN0Pw==","correct_answer":"SG9uc2h1","incorrect_answers":["SG9ra2FpZG8=","U2hpa29rdQ==","S3l1c2h1"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIE5ldyBZb3JrIFRpbWVzIHNsb2dhbiBpcywg4oCcQWxsIHRoZSBOZXdzIFRoYXTigJlzIEZpdCB0b+KApuKAnQ==","correct_answer":"UHJpbnQ=","incorrect_answers":["RGlnZXN0","TG9vaw==","UmVhZA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gU3RhciBUcmVrOiBUaGUgTmV4dCBHZW5lcmF0aW9uLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIERhdGEncyBjYXQ\/","correct_answer":"U3BvdA==","incorrect_answers":["TWl0dGVucw==","VG9t","S2l0dHk="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc21hbGxlc3QgY291bnRyeSBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ\/","correct_answer":"VmF0aWNhbiBDaXR5","incorrect_answers":["TWFsZGl2ZXM=","TW9uYWNv","TWFsdGE="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhpcyBtb2JpbGUgT1MgaGVsZCB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBtYXJrZXQgc2hhcmUgaW4gMjAxMi4=","correct_answer":"aU9T","incorrect_answers":["QW5kcm9pZA==","QmxhY2tCZXJyeQ==","U3ltYmlhbg=="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSSBiZWdpbj8=","correct_answer":"MTkxNA==","incorrect_answers":["MTkwNQ==","MTkxOQ==","MTkyNQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gIk92ZXJ3YXRjaCIsIHdoaWNoIGhlcm8gaXMgYWJsZSB0byB3YWxscmlkZT8=","correct_answer":"THVjaW8=","incorrect_answers":["UmVpbmhhcmR0","U29tYnJh","TWVyY3k="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IG9sZCB3YXMgQWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIHdoZW4gaGUgZGllZD8=","correct_answer":"NTY=","incorrect_answers":["NDM=","NjU=","NDc="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"Rm9yIHRoZSBmaWxtICJSYWlkZXJzIG9mIFRoZSBMb3N0IEFyayIsIHdoYXQgd2FzIEhhcnJpc29uIEZvcmQgc2ljayB3aXRoIGR1cmluZyB0aGUgZmlsbWluZyBvZiB0aGUgQ2Fpcm8gY2hhc2U\/","correct_answer":"RHlzZW50ZXJ5","incorrect_answers":["QW5lbWlh","Q29uc3RpcGF0aW9u","QWNpZCBSZWZsdXgg"]},
{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBicmVlZCBvZiBkb2cgd2FzICdNYXJsZXknIGluIHRoZSBmaWxtICdNYXJsZXkgJiBNZSc\/","correct_answer":"TGFicmFkb3IgUmV0cmlldmVy","incorrect_answers":["R29sZGVuIFJldHJpZXZlcg==","RGFsbWF0aWFu","U2hpYmEgSW51"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSBkaWQgIlNvbmljIFRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyIgbWFrZSBoaXMgZmlyc3QgYXBwZWFyYW5jZSBpbj8=","correct_answer":"UmFkIE1vYmlsZQ==","incorrect_answers":["U29uaWMgVGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n","U3VwZXIgTWFyaW8gNjQ=","TWVnYSBNYW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggcG9wdWxhciBGaXJzdCBQZXJzb24gU2hvb3RlciAoRlBTKSBmcmFuY2hpc2UsIGdvdCBhIFJlYWwgVGltZSBTdHJhdGVneSAoUlRTKSBnYW1lIGRldmVsb3BlZCBiYXNlZCBvbiBpdHMgdW5pdmVyc2U\/","correct_answer":"SGFsbw==","incorrect_answers":["QmF0dGxlZmllbGQ=","Q2FsbCBvZiBEdXR5","Qm9yZGVybGFuZHM="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"S2luZyBIZW5yeSBWSUlJIHdhcyB0aGUgc2Vjb25kIG1vbmFyY2ggb2Ygd2hpY2ggRXVyb3BlYW4gcm95YWwgaG91c2U\/","correct_answer":"VHVkb3I=","incorrect_answers":["WW9yaw==","U3R1YXJ0","TGFuY2FzdGVy"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggY29tcGFueSBkaWQgVmFsdmUgY29vcGVyYXRlIHdpdGggaW4gdGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHRoZSBWaXZlPw==","correct_answer":"SFRD","incorrect_answers":["T2N1bHVz","R29vZ2xl","UmF6ZXI="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCdzIHRoZSBuYW1lIG9mIEJhdG1hbidzICBwYXJlbnRzPw==","correct_answer":"VGhvbWFzICYgTWFydGhh","incorrect_answers":["Sm9leSAmIEphY2tpZQ==","SmFzb24gJiBTYXJhaA==","VG9kZCAmIE1pcmE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGhhZCBhIDE5NjkgdG9wIDUgaGl0IHdpdGggdGhlIHNvbmcsICAnQSBCb3kgTmFtZWQgU3VlJz8=","correct_answer":"Sm9obm55IENhc2g=","incorrect_answers":["Qm9iIER5bGFu","V2lsbGllIE5lbHNvbg==","S3JpcyBLcmlzdG9mZmVyc29u"]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAiTVAiIHN0YW5kIGZvciBpbiBNUDM\/","correct_answer":"TW92aW5nIFBpY3R1cmU=","incorrect_answers":["TXVzaWMgUGxheWVy","TXVsdGkgUGFzcw==","TWljcm8gUG9pbnQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkIHNpbmdlciBvZiBQZWFybCBKYW0\/","correct_answer":"RWRkaWUgVmVkZGVy","incorrect_answers":["T3p6eSBPc2JvdXJuZQ==","U3RvbmUgR29zc2FyZA==","S3VydCBDb2JhaW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgbWFwIGluY2x1ZGVkIGluIHRoZSBnYW1lIENvdW50ZXItU3RyaWtlOiBHbG9iYWwgT2ZmZW5zaXZlPw==","correct_answer":"T2lscmln","incorrect_answers":["QXNzYXVsdA==","TWlyYWdl","Q2FjaGU="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGRpcmVjdGVkIHRoZSBtb3ZpZXMgIlB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiIsICJSZXNlcnZvaXIgRG9ncyIgYW5kICJEamFuZ28gVW5jaGFpbmVkIj8=","correct_answer":"UXVlbnRpbiBUYXJhbnRpbm8=","incorrect_answers":["TWFydGluIFNjb3JjZXNl","U3RldmVuIFNwaWVsYmVyZw==","SmFtZXMgQ2FtZXJvbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSB3cml0ZXIgb2YgdGhlIGdhbWUgIkhhbGYtTGlmZSI\/","correct_answer":"TWFyYyBMYWlkbGF3","incorrect_answers":["R2FiZSBOZXdlbGw=","Um9iaW4gV2Fsa2Vy","Q2hldCBGYWxpc3plaw=="]},{"category":"VmVoaWNsZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggSXRhbGlhbiBjaXR5IGlzIGhvbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNhciBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgJ0ZpYXQnPw==","correct_answer":"VHVyaW4=","incorrect_answers":["TWFyYW5lbGxv","TW9kZW5h","Um9tZQ=="]},{"category":"Q2VsZWJyaXRpZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggYWN0cmVzcyBtYXJyaWVkIE1pY2hhZWwgRG91Z2xhcyBpbiAyMDAwPw==","correct_answer":"Q2F0aGVyaW5lIFpldGEtSm9uZXM=","incorrect_answers":["UnV0aCBKb25lcw==","UGFtIEZlcnJpcw==","U2FyYSBTdWdhcm1hbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgaW4gdGhlIEJhdG1hbiAiQXJraGFtIiBzZXJpZXM\/","correct_answer":"QXJraGFtIEFzeWx1bQ==","incorrect_answers":["QXJraGFtIEtuaWdodA==","QXJraGFtIENpdHk=","QXJraGFtIE9yaWdpbnM="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgMjAxNSBGb3JtdWxhIDEgV29ybGQgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwPw==","correct_answer":"TGV3aXMgSGFtaWx0b24=","incorrect_answers":["TmljbyBSb3NiZXJn","U2ViYXN0aWFuIFZldHRlbA==","SmVuc29uIEJ1dHRvbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggYXJ0aXN0IHJlbGVhc2VkIHRoZSAyMDEyIHNpbmdsZSAiSGFybGVtIFNoYWtlIiwgd2hpY2ggd2FzIHVzZWQgaW4gbnVtZXJvdXMgWW91VHViZSB2aWRlb3MgaW4gMjAxMz8=","correct_answer":"QmFhdWVy","incorrect_answers":["UkwgR3JpbWU=","TkdIVE1SRQ==","Rmxvc3N0cmFkYW11cw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY29yZ2kgaW4gQ293Ym95IEJlYm9wPw==","correct_answer":"RWluc3RlaW4=","incorrect_answers":["RWR3YXJk","Um9ja2V0","Sm9lbA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IG1hbnkgSGFycnkgUG90dGVyIGJvb2tzIGFyZSB0aGVyZT8=","correct_answer":"Nw==","incorrect_answers":["OA==","NQ==","Ng=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWNhbHMgJiBUaGVhdHJlcw==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdyb3RlIHRoZSBhd2FyZCB3aW5uaW5nIG11c2ljYWwgIkluIFRoZSBIZWlnaHRzIj8=","correct_answer":"TGluLU1hbnVlbCBNaXJhbmRh","incorrect_answers":["U3RldmVuIFNvbmRoZWlt","RnJhbmNpcyBTY290dCBLZXk=","Sm9obiBQaGlsbGlwcyBTb3VzYQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gbW9zdCBGUFMgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZXMgc3VjaCBhcyBDb3VudGVyLVN0cmlrZSwgc2hvb3Rpbmcgd2hpY2ggcGFydCBvZiB0aGUgYm9keSBkb2VzIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IGRhbWFnZT8=","correct_answer":"SGVhZA==","incorrect_answers":["QXJt","TGVn","Q2hlc3Q="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggZHJpdmVyIGhhcyBiZWVuIHRoZSBGb3JtdWxhIDEgd29ybGQgY2hhbXBpb24gZm9yIGEgcmVjb3JkIDcgdGltZXM\/","correct_answer":"TWljaGFlbCBTY2h1bWFjaGVy","incorrect_answers":["QXlydG9uIFNlbm5h","RmVybmFuZG8gQWxvbnNv","SmltIENsYXJr"]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggVUsgY291bnRyeSBmZWF0dXJlcyBhIGRyYWdvbiBvbiB0aGVpciBmbGFnPw==","correct_answer":"V2FsZXM=","incorrect_answers":["RW5nbGFuZA==","Tm9ydGggSXJlbGFuZA==","U2NvdGxhbmQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9hcmQgR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgZ2FtZXMgaW5jbHVkZXMgdGhlIHBocmFzZSAiRG8gbm90IHBhc3MgR28sIGRvIG5vdCBjb2xsZWN0ICQyMDAiPw==","correct_answer":"TW9ub3BvbHk=","incorrect_answers":["UGF5IERheQ==","Q2x1ZWRv","Q29wcGl0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBtYWluIHByb3RhZ29uaXN0IGluLCB0aGUgMTk4NSBmaWxtLCBCYWNrIHRvIHRoZSBGdXR1cmU\/","correct_answer":"TWFydHkgTWNGbHk=","incorrect_answers":["RW1tZXR0ICJEb2MiIEJyb3du","QmlmZiBUYW5uZW4=","R2VvcmdlIE1jRmx5"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyB0aGUgZ2FtZSBEaXNob25vcmVkIHJlbGVhc2VkPw==","correct_answer":"MjAxMg==","incorrect_answers":["MjAxMQ==","MjAwOA==","MjAxMw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpbmdyZWRpZW50cyBhcmUgcmVxdWlyZWQgdG8gbWFrZSBhIGNha2UgaW4gTWluZWNyYWZ0Pw==","correct_answer":"TWlsaywgU3VnYXIsIEVnZywgYW5kIFdoZWF0","incorrect_answers":["TWlsaywgQnJlYWQsIEVnZywgYW5kIFdoZWF0","TWlsaywgU3VnYXIgQ2FuZSwgRWdnLCBhbmQgV2hlYXQ=","TWlsaywgU3VnYXIsIGFuZCBXaGVhdA=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIGVsZW1lbnQgaW52b2x2ZWQgaW4gbWFraW5nIGh1bWFuIGJsb29kIHJlZCBpcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==","correct_answer":"SXJvbg==","incorrect_answers":["Q29wcGVy","SXJpZGl1bQ==","Q29iYWx0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHNvbmdzIGRpZCB0aGUgZ3JvdXAgIk1lbiBBdCBXb3JrIiBOT1QgbWFrZT8=","correct_answer":"U2FmZXR5IERhbmNl","incorrect_answers":["RG93biBVbmRlcg==","V2hvIENhbiBJdCBCZSBOb3c\/","SXQncyBhIE1pc3Rha2U="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gR2FtZSBvZiBUaHJvbmVzLCB3aGF0IGNvbnRpbmVudCBsaWVzIGFjcm9zcyB0aGUgTmFycm93IFNlYSBmcm9tIFdlc3Rlcm9zPw==","correct_answer":"RXNzb3M=","incorrect_answers":["RWFzdGVyb3M=","V2VzdGVyZWFzdA==","RXN1bnRvcw=="]},{"category":"TXl0aG9sb2d5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIGdyZWVrIGdvZCBQb3NlaWRvbiB3YXMgdGhlIGdvZCBvZiB3aGF0Pw==","correct_answer":"VGhlIFNlYQ==","incorrect_answers":["V2Fy","U3Vu","RmlyZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgdGhyZWUgaGVhZGVkIGRvZyBpbiBIYXJyeSBQb3R0ZXIgYW5kIHRoZSBTb3JjZXJlcidzIFN0b25lPw==","correct_answer":"Rmx1ZmZ5","incorrect_answers":["U3Bpa2U=","UG9vZnk=","U3BvdA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgaG9tZXdvcmxkIG9mIHRoZSBFbGl0ZXMgZnJvbSBIYWxvPw==","correct_answer":"U2FuZ2hlbGlvcw==","incorrect_answers":["VGU=","RG9pc2Fj","RWF5bg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggTmlydmFuYSBhbGJ1bSBoYWQgYSBuYWtlZCBiYWJ5IG9uIHRoZSBjb3Zlcj8=","correct_answer":"TmV2ZXJtaW5k","incorrect_answers":["QmxlYWNo","SW4gVXRlcm8=","SW5jZXN0aWNpZGU="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdhcyBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgc29uZyAiV29yZHMiIGJ5IEZlaW50PyA=","correct_answer":"TGF1cmEgQnJlaG0=","incorrect_answers":["QW5uYSBZdmV0dGUg","RGFueWthIE5hZGVhdQ==","VmVlbGE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gUnVzdCwgaG93IG1hbnkgVGltZWQgRXhwbG9zaXZlIENoYXJnZXMgZG9lcyBpdCB0YWtlIHRvIGRlc3Ryb3kgYSBMYWRkZXIgSGF0Y2g\/","correct_answer":"MQ==","incorrect_answers":["Mw==","Mg==","NQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDIwMTIgZmlsbSwgIlRoZSBMb3JheCIsIHdobyBpcyB0aGUgYW50YWdvbmlzdD8=","correct_answer":"QWxveXNpdXMgTydIYXJl","incorrect_answers":["VGVkIFdpZ2dpbnM=","VGhlIE9uY2UtTGVy","R3JhbW15IE5vcm1h"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBTdXBlciBNYXJpbyBCcm9zLiByZWxlYXNlZD8=","correct_answer":"MTk4NQ==","incorrect_answers":["MTk4Mw==","MTk4Nw==","MTk4Ng=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIENhcnRvb24gTmV0d29yayBzZXJpZXMgIlJlZ3VsYXIgU2hvdyI\/","correct_answer":"Si4gRy4gUXVpbnRlbA==","incorrect_answers":["QmVuIEJvY3F1ZWxldA==","UGVuZGxldG9uIFdhcmQ=","UmViZWNjYSBTdWdhcg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"IlRoZSBQb3RhdG8gU2FjayIgd2FzIGEgY29sbGVjdGlvbiBvZiBpbmRpZSBnYW1lcyByZWxlYXNlZCBvbiBTdGVhbSBpbiAyMDExIGFzIGEgcHJvbW90aW9uIGZvciB3aGljaCBnYW1lPw==","correct_answer":"UG9ydGFsIDI=","incorrect_answers":["TGVmdCA0IERlYWQgMg==","SGFsZi1MaWZlIDM=","RG90YSAy"]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlICJUcmFpbCBvZiBUZWFycyIgd2FzIGEgcmVzdWx0IG9mIHdoaWNoIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50J3MgSW5kaWFuIFJlbW92YWwgUG9saWN5Pw==","correct_answer":"QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24=","incorrect_answers":["SGFycnkgUy4gVHJ1bWFu","TWFydGluIFZhbiBCdXJlbg==","Sm9obiBRdWluY3kgQWRhbXM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"IlRoZSBTaW5naW5nIENvd2JveSIgR2VuZSBBdXRyeSBpcyBjcmVkaXRlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBmaXJzdCByZWNvcmRpbmcgZm9yIGFsbCBidXQgd2hpY2ggY2xhc3NpYyBDaHJpc3RtYXMgamluZ2xlPw==","correct_answer":"V2hpdGUgQ2hyaXN0bWFz","incorrect_answers":["RnJvc3R5IHRoZSBTbm93bWFu","UnVkb2xwaCB0aGUgUmVkLU5vc2VkIFJlaW5kZWVy","SGVyZSBDb21lcyBTYW50YSBDbGF1cw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBmcm9tICJTcG9uZ2VCb2IgU3F1YXJlUGFudHMiIGlzIG5vdCBhIHNxdWlkPw==","correct_answer":"R2FyeQ==","incorrect_answers":["T3J2aWxsaWU=","U3F1aWR3YXJk","U3F1aWRldHRl"]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB5ZWFyIGRpZCBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSSBiZWdpbj8=","correct_answer":"MTkxNA==","incorrect_answers":["MTkwNQ==","MTkxOQ==","MTkyNQ=="]},{"category":"UG9saXRpY3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"Rm9ybWVyIFVuaXRlZCBTdGF0ZXMgUHJlc2lkZW50IEJpbGwgQ2xpbnRvbiBmYW1vdXNseSBwbGF5ZWQgd2hpY2ggaW5zdHJ1bWVudD8=","correct_answer":"U2F4b3Bob25l","incorrect_answers":["QmFyaXRvbmUgaG9ybg==","UGlhbm8=","VmlvbGlu"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgbm90IGEgd29uZGVyIHdlYXBvbiBpbiAiQ2FsbCBPZiBEdXR5OiBab21iaWVzIj8=","correct_answer":"UjExNSBSZXNvbmF0b3I=","incorrect_answers":["R0taLTQ1IE1rMw==","UmF5IEd1bg==","U2NhdmVuZ2Vy"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYm9zcyByb3VuZCBmZWF0dXJlZCBpbiB0aGUgIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIgbWFwICJGaXZlIj8=","correct_answer":"VGhlIFBlbnRhZ29uIFRoaWVm","incorrect_answers":["SGVsbGhvdW5kcw==","SnVtcGluZyBKYWNrcw==","TmFwYWxtIFpvbWJpZQ=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogTWF0aGVtYXRpY3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY29ycmVjdCBvcmRlciBvZiBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGZvciBzb2x2aW5nIGVxdWF0aW9ucz8=","correct_answer":"UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9uLCBBZGRpdGlvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24=","incorrect_answers":["QWRkaXRpb24sIE11bHRpcGxpY2F0aW9uLCBEaXZpc2lvbiwgU3VidHJhY3Rpb24sIEFkZGl0aW9uLCBQYXJlbnRoZXNlcw==","UGFyZW50aGVzZXMsIEV4cG9uZW50cywgQWRkaXRpb24sIFN1YnN0cmFjdGlvbiwgTXVsdGlwbGljYXRpb24sIERpdmlzaW9u","VGhlIG9yZGVyIGluIHdoaWNoIHRoZSBvcGVyYXRpb25zIGFyZSB3cml0dGVuLg=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyBUYXNtYW5pYT8=","correct_answer":"QW4gQXVzdHJhbGlhbiBTdGF0ZQ==","incorrect_answers":["QSBmbGF2b3Igb2YgQmVuIGFuZCBKZXJyeSdzIGljZS1jcmVhbQ==","QSBQc3ljaG9sb2dpY2FsIERpc29yZGVy","VGhlIE5hbWUgb2YgYSBXYXJuZXIgQnJvdGhlcnMgQ2FydG9vbiBDaGFyYWN0ZXI="]},{"category":"Q2VsZWJyaXRpZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"Qnkgd2hpY2ggbmFtZSBpcyBSYW1vbiBFc3RldmV6IGJldHRlciBrbm93biBhcz8=","correct_answer":"TWFydGluIFNoZWVu","incorrect_answers":["Q2hhcmxpZSBTaGVlbg==","UmFtb24gU2hlZW4=","RW1pbGlvIEVzdGV2ZXo="]},
{"category":"UG9saXRpY3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvc2UgMjAxNiBwcmVzaWRlbnRpYWwgY2FtcGFpZ24gc2xvZ2FuIHdhcyAiTWFrZSBBbWVyaWNhIEdyZWF0IEFnYWluIj8=","correct_answer":"RG9uYWxkIFRydW1w","incorrect_answers":["VGVkIENydXo=","TWFyY28gUnViaW8=","QmVybmllIFNhbmRlcnM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gU291dGggUGFyaywgd2hhdCBpcyBTdGFuJ3Mgc3VybmFtZT8=","correct_answer":"TWFyc2g=","incorrect_answers":["U3RvdGNo","QnJvZmxvdnNraQ==","VHdlYWs="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggR3JlZWsgbGV0dGVyIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlICJIYWxmLUxpZmUiIGxvZ28\/","correct_answer":"TGFtYmRh","incorrect_answers":["T21lZ2E=","QWxwaGE=","U2lnbWE="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgYm9uZXMgaXMgaGFyZGVzdCB0byBicmVhaz8=","correct_answer":"RmVtdXI=","incorrect_answers":["Q3Jhbml1bQ==","SHVtZXJ1cw==","VGliaWE="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggZWxlbWVudCBoYXMgdGhlIGNoZW1pY2FsIHN5bWJvbCAnRmUnPw==","correct_answer":"SXJvbg==","incorrect_answers":["R29sZA==","U2lsdmVy","VGlu"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvJ3MgdGhlIHZvaWNlIGFjdG9yIGZvciBUaHJhbGwgaW4gdGhlIFdhcmNyYWZ0IGdhbWUgc2VyaWVzPw==","correct_answer":"Q2hyaXMgTWV0emVu","incorrect_answers":["QmVuIEFmZmxlY2s=","SmFzb24gRGVydWxv","SmltIENhcnJleQ=="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggRW5nbGlzaCBmb290YmFsbCBjbHViIGhhcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgJ1RoZSBGb3hlcyc\/","correct_answer":"TGVpY2VzdGVyIENpdHk=","incorrect_answers":["Tm9ydGhhbXB0b24gVG93bg==","QnJhZGZvcmQgQ2l0eQ==","V2VzdCBCcm9td2ljaCBBbGJpb24="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBkb2VzIHRoZSAiTVAiIHN0YW5kIGZvciBpbiBNUDM\/","correct_answer":"TW92aW5nIFBpY3R1cmU=","incorrect_answers":["TXVzaWMgUGxheWVy","TXVsdGkgUGFzcw==","TWljcm8gUG9pbnQ="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcGxheWVyIGNsYXNzIGluIFRlYW0gRm9ydHJlc3MgMj8=","correct_answer":"SGVhbGVy","incorrect_answers":["RGVtb21hbg==","UHlybw==","U3B5"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IHdvdWxkIG9uZSBzYXkgZ29vZGJ5ZSBpbiBTcGFuaXNoPw==","correct_answer":"QWRpw7Nz","incorrect_answers":["IEhvbGE=","QXUgUmV2b2ly","U2FsaXI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9hcmQgR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"T24gYSBzdGFuZGFyZCBNb25vcG9seSBib2FyZCwgd2hpY2ggc3F1YXJlIGlzIGRpYWdvbmFsbHkgb3Bwb3NpdGUgJ0dvJz8g","correct_answer":"RnJlZSBQYXJraW5n","incorrect_answers":["R28gdG8gSmFpbA==","SmFpbA==","VGhlIEVsZWN0cmljIENvbXBhbnk="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3b3JkIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIGxldHRlciAnVCcgaW4gdGhlIE5BVE8gcGhvbmV0aWMgYWxwaGFiZXQ\/","correct_answer":"VGFuZ28=","incorrect_answers":["VGFyZ2V0","VGF4aQ==","VHVya2V5"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggZmFtb3VzIHNweSBub3ZlbGlzdCB3cm90ZSB0aGUgY2hpbGRyZW5zJyBzdG9yeSAiQ2hpdHR5LUNoaXR0eS1CYW5nLUJhbmciPw==","correct_answer":"SWFuIEZsZW1pbmc=","incorrect_answers":["Sm9zZXBoIENvbnJhZA==","Sm9obiBCdWNoYW4=","R3JhaGFtIEdyZWVuZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"R3JhbnQgR3VzdGluIHBsYXlzIHdoaWNoIHN1cGVyaGVybyBvbiB0aGUgQ1cgc2hvdyBvZiB0aGUgc2FtZSBuYW1lPw==","correct_answer":"VGhlIEZsYXNo","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIEFycm93","QmxhY2sgQ2FuYXJ5","RGFyZWRldmls"]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIHByb2dyYW1taW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlIEphdmEsIHdoaWNoIG9mIHRoZXNlIGtleXdvcmRzIHdvdWxkIHlvdSBwdXQgb24gYSB2YXJpYWJsZSB0byBtYWtlIHN1cmUgaXQgZG9lc24ndCBnZXQgbW9kaWZpZWQ\/","correct_answer":"RmluYWw=","incorrect_answers":["U3RhdGlj","UHJpdmF0ZQ==","UHVibGlj"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2hhcGUgb2YgdGhlIHRveSBpbnZlbnRlZCBieSBIdW5nYXJpYW4gcHJvZmVzc29yIEVybsWRIFJ1YmlrPw==","correct_answer":"Q3ViZQ==","incorrect_answers":["U3BoZXJl","Q3lsaW5kZXI=","UHlyYW1pZA=="]},{"category":"TXl0aG9sb2d5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhpcyBHcmVlayBnb2RkZXNzJ3MgbmFtZSB3YXMgY2hvc2VuIGZvciB0aGUgZHdhcmYgcGxhbmV0IHJlc3BvbnNpYmxlIGZvciBkaXNjb3JkIG9uIFBsdXRvJ3MgY2xhc3NpZmljYXRpb24gYW1vbmdzdCBhc3Ryb25vbWVycy4=","correct_answer":"RXJpcw==","incorrect_answers":["Q2hhcm9u","Q2VyZXM=","RHlzbm9taWE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"RmluaXNoIHRoZXNlIGx5cmljcyBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDE2IHNvbmcgIlBhbmRhIiBieSBEZXNpaWduZXI6ICJJIGdvdCBicm9hZHMgaW4gX19fX19fXyIu","correct_answer":"QXRsYW50YQ==","incorrect_answers":["U2F2YW5uYWg=","QXVndXN0YQ==","TWFyaWV0dGE="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gR3JhbmQgVGhlZnQgQXV0byBWLCB3aGF0IHdhcyBNaWNoYWVsIERlIFNhbnRhJ3MgZm9ybWVyIHN1cm5hbWU\/","correct_answer":"VG93bmxleQ==","incorrect_answers":["RGUgU2FudG9z","V2F0c29u","U2ltcHNvbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHZvaWNlcyBmb3IgUnVieSBpbiB0aGUgYW5pbWF0ZWQgc2VyaWVzIFJXQlk\/","correct_answer":"TGluZHNheSBKb25lcw==","incorrect_answers":["VGFyYSBTdHJvbmc=","SmVzc2ljYSBOaWdyaQ==","SGF5ZGVuIFBhbmV0dGllcmU="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggVHdpdGNoIHN0cmVhbWVyIGlzIHRoZSB2b2NhbGlzdCBmb3IgUmVkIFZveD8=","correct_answer":"VmluZXNhdWNl","incorrect_answers":["VGhlOEJpdERydW1tZXI=","TElSSUs=","U29kYXBvcHBpbg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbW92aWVzIGRpZCBKZWZmIEJyaWRnZXMgbm90IHN0YXIgaW4\/","correct_answer":"VGhlIEhhdGVmdWwgRWlnaHQ=","incorrect_answers":["VHJvbjogTGVnYWN5","VGhlIEdpdmVy","VHJ1ZSBHcml0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IERpc25leSBtb3ZpZSB0byB1c2UgQ0dJPw==","correct_answer":"VGhlIEJsYWNrIENhdWxkcm9u","incorrect_answers":["VHJvbg==","VG95IFN0b3J5","RmFudGFzaWE="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpbmFsIHNjb3JlIG9mIHRoZSBHZXJtYW55IHZzLiBCcmF6aWwgMjAxNCBGSUZBIFdvcmxkIEN1cCBtYXRjaD8=","correct_answer":"NyAtIDE=","incorrect_answers":["MCAtIDE=","MyAtIDQ=","MTYgLSAw"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgRnJlbmNoIHdvcmQgZm9yICJoYXQiPw==","correct_answer":"Q2hhcGVhdQ==","incorrect_answers":["Qm9ubmV0","IMOJY2hhcnBl","IENhc3F1ZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgY2hhcmFjdGVycyBpcyB0aGUgbWFzY290IG9mIHRoZSB2aWRlbyBnYW1lIGNvbXBhbnkgU0VHQT8=","correct_answer":"U29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9n","incorrect_answers":["RHluYW1pdGUgSGVhZGR5","QWxleCBLaWRk","T3BhLU9wYQ=="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmlja25hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSBVUyBzdGF0ZSBEZWxhd2FyZT8=","correct_answer":"VGhlIEZpcnN0IFN0YXRl","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIEZpZnRpZXRoIFN0YXRl","VGhlIFNlY29uZCBTdGF0ZQ==","VGhlIFNpeHRlZW50aCBTdGF0ZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGlzIHRoZSBsZWFkZXIgb2YgVGVhbSBNeXN0aWMgaW4gUG9rw6ltb24gR28\/","correct_answer":"QmxhbmNoZQ==","incorrect_answers":["Q2FuZGVsYQ==","U3Bhcms=","V2lsbG93"]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIG1lZGljYWwgdGVybSBmb3IgdGhlIGJlbGx5IGJ1dHRvbiBpcyB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nPw==","correct_answer":"VW1iaWxpY3Vz","incorrect_answers":["TmV2dXM=","TmFyZXM=","UGF4aWxsdXM="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGluIFB1bHAgRmljdGlvbiBzYXlzICJObywgdGhleSBnb3QgdGhlIG1ldHJpYyBzeXN0ZW0gdGhlcmUsIHRoZXkgd291bGRuJ3Qga25vdyB3aGF0IHRoZSBmdWNrIGEgUXVhcnRlciBQb3VuZGVyIGlzLiI=","correct_answer":"VmluY2VudCBWZWdh","incorrect_answers":["SnVsZXMgV2lubmZpZWxk","SmltbWllIERpbW1pY2s=","QnV0Y2ggQ29vbGlkZ2U="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gU3VwZXJuYXR1cmFsLCB3aGF0J3MgaXMgU2FtJ3MgYnJvdGhlcnMgbmFtZT8=","correct_answer":"RGVhbg==","incorrect_answers":["RGF2ZQ==","U3RldmU=","TWlrZQ=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4tb3duZWQgYnJld2VyeSBsZWQgdGhlIGNvdW50cnkgaW4gc2FsZXMgYnkgdm9sdW1lIGluIDIwMTU\/","correct_answer":"RC4gRy4gWXVlbmdsaW5nIGFuZCBTb24sIEluYw==","incorrect_answers":["QW5oZXVzZXIgQnVzY2g=","Qm9zdG9uIEJlZXIgQ29tcGFueQ==","TWlsbGVyIENvb3Jz"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIDIwMDIgZmlsbSAiMjggRGF5cyBMYXRlciIgaXMgbWFpbmx5IHNldCBpbiB3aGljaCBFdXJvcGVhbiBjb3VudHJ5Pw==","correct_answer":"VW5pdGVkIEtpbmdkb20=","incorrect_answers":["RnJhbmNl","SXRhbHk=","R2VybWFueQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"S2FueWUgV2VzdCdzICJHb2xkIERpZ2dlciIgZmVhdHVyZWQgd2hpY2ggT3NjYXItd2lubmluZyBhY3Rvcj8=","correct_answer":"SmFtaWUgRm94eA==","incorrect_answers":["QWxlYyBCYWxkd2lu","RHdheW5lIEpvaG5zb24=","IEJydWNlIFdpbGxpcw=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"NzElIG9mIHRoZSBFYXJ0aCdzIHN1cmZhY2UgaXMgbWFkZSB1cCBvZg==","correct_answer":"V2F0ZXI=","incorrect_answers":["RGVzZXJ0cw==","Q29udGluZW50cw==","Rm9yZXN0cw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gQW5pbWFsIENyb3NzaW5nLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIG1hbmFnZXIgb2YgdGhlIHRvd24gc2hvcD8=","correct_answer":"VG9tIE5vb2s=","incorrect_answers":["TXIuIFJlc2V0dGk=","R3JhY2ll","Sy5LLiBTbGlkZXI="]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SG93IG1hbnkgc3RhcnMgYXJlIGZlYXR1cmVkIG9uIE5ldyBaZWFsYW5kJ3MgZmxhZz8=","correct_answer":"NA==","incorrect_answers":["NQ==","Mg==","MA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgNC1hcm1lZCBDaGFvcyBXaXRjaCBmcm9tIHRoZSAyMDE2IHZpZGVvIGdhbWUgIkJhdHRsZWJvcm4iPw==","correct_answer":"T3JlbmRp","incorrect_answers":["T3JlbmRvbw==","T3JhbmRh","UmFuZHk="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gdGhlIDIwMTIgYW5pbWF0ZWQgZmlsbSAiV29sZiBDaGlsZHJlbiIsIHdoYXQgYXJlIHRoZSBuYW1lcyBvZiB0aGUgd29sZiBjaGlsZHJlbj8=","correct_answer":"QW1lICYgWXVraQ==","incorrect_answers":["SGFuYSAmIFl1a2k=","QW1lICYgSGFuYQ==","Q2h1Y2sgJiBBbm5h"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgd29ybGQgdGhhdCB0aGUgTU1PICJSdW5lU2NhcGUiIHRha2VzIHBsYWNlIGluPw==","correct_answer":"R2llbGlub3I=","incorrect_answers":["R2xpbmRvcg==","QXplcm90aA==","WmFyb3M="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggVGVlbmFnZSBNdXRhbnQgTmluamEgVHVydGxlIHRyYWRpdGlvbmFsbHkgd2VhcnMgYW4gb3JhbmdlIGJhbmRhbmE\/","correct_answer":"TWljaGVsYW5nZWxv","incorrect_answers":["TGVvbmFyZG8=","RG9uYXRlbGxv","UmFwaGFlbA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQ2FydG9vbiAmIEFuaW1hdGlvbnM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIGNyZWF0ZWQgdGhlIENhcnRvb24gTmV0d29yayBzZXJpZXMgIlJlZ3VsYXIgU2hvdyI\/","correct_answer":"Si4gRy4gUXVpbnRlbA==","incorrect_answers":["QmVuIEJvY3F1ZWxldA==","UGVuZGxldG9uIFdhcmQ=","UmViZWNjYSBTdWdhcg=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggZnJhbmNoaXNlIHdhcyBOT1QgZmVhdHVyZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTUgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZSAiTGVnbyBEaW1lbnNpb25zIj8=","correct_answer":"QnJlYWtpbmcgQmFk","incorrect_answers":["UG9ydGFs","RG9jdG9yIFdobw==","QmFjayB0byB0aGUgRnV0dXJl"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVGVsZXZpc2lvbg==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"QnJpdGlzaCBhY3RvciBEYXZpZCBNb3JyaXNzZXkgc3RhcnMgYXMgd2hpY2ggcm9sZSBpbiAiVGhlIFdhbGtpbmcgRGVhZCI\/","correct_answer":"VGhlIEdvdmVybm9y","incorrect_answers":["TmVnYW4=","UmljayBHcmltZXM=","RGFyeWwgRGl4b24="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hvIHdhcyBhbW9uZyB0aG9zZSBraWxsZWQgaW4gdGhlIDIwMTAgU21vbGVuc2ssIFJ1c3NpYSBwbGFuZSBjcmFzaCB0cmFnZWR5Pw==","correct_answer":"VGhlIFBvbGlzaCBQcmVzaWRlbnQ=","incorrect_answers":["UG9wZSBKb2huIFBhdWwgSUk=","QmFuZy1EaW5nIE93","QWxiZXJ0IFB1dGlu"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGV2ZXIgTG9uZG9uIFVuZGVyZ3JvdW5kIGxpbmUgdG8gYmUgYnVpbHQ\/","correct_answer":"TWV0cm9wb2xpdGFuIExpbmU=","incorrect_answers":["Q2lyY2xlIExpbmU=","QmFrZXJsb28gTGluZQ==","VmljdG9yaWEgTGluZQ=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogR2FkZ2V0cw==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERWRCBpbnZlbnRlZD8=","correct_answer":"MTk5NQ==","incorrect_answers":["MjAwMA==","MTk5MA==","MTk4MA=="]},{"category":"U3BvcnRz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"V2hpY2ggdGVhbSBoYXMgd29uIHRoZSBtb3N0IFN0YW5sZXkgQ3VwcyBpbiB0aGUgTkhMPw==","correct_answer":"TW9udHJlYWwgQ2FuYWRpYW5z","incorrect_answers":["Q2hpY2FnbyBCbGFja2hhd2tz","VG9yb250byBNYXBsZSBMZWFmcw==","RGV0cm9pdCBSZWQgV2luZ3M="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"SW4gIkNhbGwgT2YgRHV0eTogWm9tYmllcyIsIHdoYXQgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIG1hY2hpbmUgdGhhdCB1cGdyYWRlcyB3ZWFwb25zPw==","correct_answer":"UGFjay1BLVB1bmNo","incorrect_answers":["V3VuZGVyZml6eg==","R2Vyc2NoIERldmljZQ==","TXVsZSBLaWNr"]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"ZWFzeQ==","question":"VGhlIEMgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugd2FzIGNyZWF0ZWQgYnkgdGhpcyBBbWVyaWNhbiBjb21wdXRlciBzY2llbnRpc3QuIA==","correct_answer":"RGVubmlzIFJpdGNoaWU=","incorrect_answers":["VGltIEJlcm5lcnMgTGVl","YWwtS2h3xIFyaXptxKs=","V2lsbGlzIFdhcmU="]},
]}
